In this video, I will show you how to make a three-dimensional bedhead effect.
Welcome to MarvelousDesigner's tutorial video on how to make a three-dimensional bedhead effect.
First, open the previous bedhead file you made.
You can also download this file from the shortcut at the bottom of this video.
To make a three-dimensional bedhead effect, select the two lines on the front of the bedhead.
In the menu bar on the right-hand side, select the line to be made according to the curve.
The line to be made according to the curve will be divided into two parts.
To create a three-dimensional bedhead effect, select the front of the bedhead and the outer part of the bedhead.
Then select the new bedhead and make a joint.
After making a joint, you can modify the size of the bedhead separately without affecting other bedheads.
Then freeze the other two layers of bedhead.
Open the model and let the bedhead be divided.
In order to make a three-dimensional bedhead effect, you need to stretch the outer part of the bedhead horizontally.
In this way, you can have enough volume to be opened.
Stretch it again and turn on the model to check the effect.
Change the pressure to 10 to get the effect of a three-dimensional bedhead.
Since the inflow effect is not more obvious, increase the pressure to 50 to get a more obvious inflow effect.
Checking the bedhead, you will see that the bedhead between the outer layer and the middle layer of the panel is biased.
The bedhead between the outer layer and the middle layer of the panel is parallel to the entire circle of the panel.
Therefore, the bedhead is biased only when the horizontal width is widened.
If you're using an immigrated bedhead, select the bedhead in the center.
The width of the möbler or the width of the bedhead is equal to the width of the upper layer of the panel.
In order to create a more accurate bedhead, select the upper and lower edge of the upper and lower layers of the two layers panel, and select an increase point at the intersection point in the menu to draw it in.
The two lines are now in this position.
These two lines will be cut off according to the internal line, which is convenient for sewing.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the two sides together first.
Then use the thread sewing machine to sew the top and bottom together.
After sewing, the bias of the panel line disappears and is sewn to the correct position.
Next, let's create the effect of straightening.
Stretch the outermost panel line.
After starting the simulation, the outermost panel line is stretched by the beam, which will produce some creases.
Reduce the force from 0.5 to 0.5 to obtain a better creasing effect.
See you in the next video, bye.